Guide to the Jean Kilbourne Papers, 1918-2014 and undated RL.10982
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2006 and undated; 9; 11 boxes
  - RL10982-DVD-0038. 2014-2017. The Sex Files. dvd. Original. 2004-11 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0039. 2014-2017. Garland Waller Interview. dvd. Original. 1984 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0040. 2014-2017. Archive Data/Media #1. dvd. Original. 1970s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0041. 2014-2017. Data Disc #2. dvd. Original. 1970s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0042. 2014-2017. Data Disc #3. dvd. Original. 1980s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0043. 2014-2017. Data Disc #4. dvd. Original. 1980s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0044. 2014-2017. Data Disc #5. dvd. Original. 1980s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0045. 2014-2017. Data Disc #6. dvd. Original. 1980s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0046. 2014-2017. Data Disc #7. dvd. Original. 1990s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0047. 2014-2017. Data Disc #8. dvd. Original. 1990s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0048. 2014-2017. Data Disc #9. dvd. Original. 2000s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0049. 2014-2017. Data Disc #10. dvd. Original. 2000s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0050. 2014-2017. Data Disc #11. dvd. Original. 2000s (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-Beta-0001. 2014-2017. Mourir a petit feu 3. (Killing Us Softly 3). TRT 34:32. betacam. Original. 2004 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-Beta-0002. 2014-2017. Killing Us Softly 3. TRT 34:32. Master. betacam. Original. Undated. (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-Beta-0003. 2014-2017. Calling the Shots. TRT 29:00. Master. betacam. Original. Undated. (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-Beta-0004. 2014-2017. Still Killing Us Softly. betacam. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-CD-0001. 2014-2017. Living Dialogues with Duncan Campbell and Coleman Barks. 8 CD Set. TRT 362:49. compact disc. Original. 2001 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-CD-0002. 2014-2017. Ethics in Advertising. TRT 58:30. compact disc. Original. 2005 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-CD-0003. 2014-2017. Once Upon a Loss: A New Look At Cinderella. TRT 49:00. compact disc. Original. 1995 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0001. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #1. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0002. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #2. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0003. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #3. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0004. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #4. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0005. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #5-National. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0006. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #6. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0007. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #7. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0008. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #8. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0009. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #9. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0010. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #10. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0011. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #11. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0012. 2014-2017. Jean K #1. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0013. 2014-2017. Jean K #2. mini-dv. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0014. 2014-2017. Today Show. mini-dv. Original. 1979 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0015. 2014-2017. Joel Show: Woman Adv. mini-dv. Original. 1979 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0016. 2014-2017. The Joe Oteri Show. mini-dv. Original. 1979 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0017. 2014-2017. Weekday. mini-dv. Original. 1981 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0018. 2014-2017. Up to the Minute. CBS-TV. mini-dv. Original. 1981 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0019. 2014-2017. New England Today: Alcohol Advertising. mini-dv. Original. 1985 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0020. 2014-2017. Last Word. mini-dv. Original. 1982 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0021. 2014-2017. Slide Presentation in Dallas. mini-dv. Original. 1978 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0022. 2014-2017. Evening Magazine. mini-dv. Original. 1978 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0023. 2014-2017. WLVI Boston. New England. mini-dv. Original. 1978 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0024. 2014-2017. Alcohol in Advertising. mini-dv. Original. 1981 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0025. 2014-2017. Point of View. mini-dv. Original. 1981 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-MiniDV-0026. 2014-2017. At Noon. mini-dv. Original. 1979 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-8mm-0001. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0002. 2014-2017. Gaylord Can 16400. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0003. 2014-2017. Clear Leader Film. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0004. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0005. 2014-2017. Tape 2: Salad Thtrough for Baby. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0006. 2014-2017. Tape 3: M and M through Children. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0007. 2014-2017. Hat Time-John Ryan. Pennies- Max Grealer and Doug Knowles. Cars- Doug Knowles. Squares- Debbie Kinniso and Jaff Morgan. Worm- Dana Piccian, Kathy Pineo and Steve Brookfield. Clay- Alan Reed and Other Name. Student Projects. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0008. 2014-2017. The Chase- Scott McCurdy and Joe Wright. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0009. 2014-2017. The Good Boy Friend. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0010. 2014-2017. Jim Chamness. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0011. 2014-2017. Tape 1: Walk on by- Through the Chase. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0012. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0013. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0014. 2014-2017. Timex- Bob Hossey, Nancy Delaney and Joanne Bentiny. Weepy Man- Bill Mclaryliln and Beth Zelms. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0015. 2014-2017. Salad. Flote Their Pipecleaners. Equipment Rebellion. Machine. The Math. Student Projects. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0016. 2014-2017. Untitled. Labelled Junk for Practice. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0017. 2014-2017. Untitled. Labelled Junk for Practice. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0018. 2014-2017. The Making of Airplane. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0019. 2014-2017. SF and LA 1970- end with Disneyland. Student Project. 8mm. Original. 1970 (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0020. 2014-2017. Testing the Camera. Land on Shots of C-11. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0021. 2014-2017. Louis- Martha's Vineyard and Hanesville. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0022. 2014-2017. Louis- MV. 2nd Half Blank. Student Project. 8mm. Original. 1971 (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0023. 2014-2017. Magazine St. 2nd Half Black. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0024. 2014-2017. Genevieve- Love in the Deep Blue. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0025. 2014-2017. Car Theft. Anyone Want to Buy A Used Drum. Student Projects. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0026. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0027. 2014-2017. Hung-ary- Venice. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0028. 2014-2017. M + M. Blowery Kisses. The Joker. Chess Does Not Pay. Motorcycle. Teddy Bear. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0029. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0030. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0031. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0032. 2014-2017. Soundtracks for Final Projects. Student Projects. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0033. 2014-2017. Soundtrack- Dave and Chuck's Film (Side 1). Mark Vanderwater (Side 2). Student Projects. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0034. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0035. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0036. 2014-2017. The Sadists. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0037. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0038. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0039. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0040. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0041. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0042. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0043. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0044. 2014-2017. Untitled. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0045. 2014-2017. Untitled. Barbie and Ken. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0046. 2014-2017. Untitled. Brian Carlisle. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-8mm-0047. 2014-2017. Untitled. Mickey and Barbie. Student Project. 8mm. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-Cass-0001. 2014-2017. Jean Kilbourne (Side 1). Student Project. audiocassette. Original. Undated. (Box AV10)
  - RL10982-16mm-0001. 2014-2017. Killing Us Softly. 16mm. Original. Undated. (Reel 1)
  - RL10982-16mm-0002. 2014-2017. Still Killing Us Softly. 16mm. Original. Undated. (Reel 2)
  - RL10982-16mm-0003. 2014-2017. Calling the Shots: The Advertising of Alcohol. 16mm. Original. Undated. (Reel 3)
  - RL10982-16mm-0004. 2014-2017. Still Killing Us Softly. 16mm. Original. Undated. (Reel 4)
  - RL10982-16mm-0005. 2014-2017. Still Killing Us Softly. 16mm. Original. Undated. (Reel 5)
  - RL10982-16mm-0006. 2014-2017. Untitled. 16mm. Original. Undated. (Reel 6)
  - RL10982-1Inch-0001. 2014-2017. Still Killing Us Softly. TRT 31:29. 1-inch. Original. Undated. (Reel 7)
  - RL10982-VHS-0208. 2014-2017. Flash Point: Life Skills Through the Lens of Media Literacy. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0209. 2014-2017. Flash Point II: Close-Up on Civil Rights. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0210. 2014-2017. Flash Point III: Close-Up on Underage Drinking. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0211. 2014-2017. Flash Point IV: Close-Up on Internet Intelligence. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0212. 2014-2017. AdSmarts A: Media and Advertising. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0213. 2014-2017. AdSmarts B: Alcohol Advertising. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0214. 2014-2017. AdSmarts C: Tobacco Advertising. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0215. 2014-2017. AdSmarts D: Media, Tobacco and Alcohol Advertising. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0216. 2014-2017. ADSmarts E: Media Action. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0217. 2014-2017. Beyond Blame: Challenging Violence in the Media. VHS. Original. 1995 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0002. 2014-2017. Beyond Blame: Challenging Violence in the Media. audiocassette. Original. 1995 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0003. 2014-2017. Thinking About Drinking 1/2: The Magic Potion/The Terrible Trap. audiocassette. Original. 1988 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0004. 2014-2017. Thinking About Drinking 3/4: The Lady Drinks/The Road to Recovery. audiocassette. Original. 1988 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0005. 2014-2017. Thinking About Drinking 5/6: One Step at a Time/A Family Disease. audiocassette. Original. 1988 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0006. 2014-2017. Thinking About Drinking 7/8: Teach Your Children Well/Business and Booze. audiocassette. Original. 1988 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0007. 2014-2017. Thinking About Drinking 9/10: Latino Perspectives/A Social History of Inebriation. audiocassette. Original. 1988 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0008. 2014-2017. Thinking About Drinking 11/12: Driving under the Influence/Media Images of Alcohol. audiocassette. Original. 1988 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-VHS-0218. 2014-2017. Communities Take Charge! VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0009. 2014-2017. Communities Take Charge!. audiocassette. Original. 1991 (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0010. 2014-2017. Media and Democracy Congress II: The State of the Media. Tape 2 of 2. audiocassette. Original. Undated. (Box AV11)
  - RL10982-Cass-0011. 2014-2017. Gender Advertisments. audiocassette. Original. Undated. (Box AV11)
- Large-format Materials, 1918-1994 and undated; 1 boxes
  - Bag, Budweiser/Steve Reichl sponsoring NACA convention, undated (Box OV1)
  - Danish anti-alcoholism posters, undated (Box OV1)
  - "Fair warning" labels presentation box, National "Tobacco or Kids" Campaign (Canada), undated (Box OV1)
  - HIram Walker inflatable point-of-sale plastic bottle, undated (Box OV1)
  - Mounted advertisements: ScotTissue, Abdulla Cigarettes, 1918 and undated (Box OV1)
  - Nude Beer poster, undated (Box OV1)
  - Scrapbook, 1977-1994 (Box OV1)
  - Snap-On Tools calendar, 1988 (Box OV1)